When we say We need This for
him we need a coverage for him always
answers us Sorry the special needs
automatic rejection that I am the primary
caregiver of my son who has autism idd
intellectual development delay and ADHD
we weren't able to find that security
until That's my friend who
recently became a manual life Agent
I said this is what I need Let's do
something for my son I know he can't do it
alone They're already
disadvantaged We want to give them every
opportunity everything that we can give
them I'm also advocating for other
parents you know this is possible right
now find a manual life agent that will
advocate for you
[Music]